/* eslint-disable max-len */

/** Glossary Queries */

export const queries = [
  {
    question: "What is TheGradStory?",
    answer:
      "TheGradStory is a comprehensive platform designed to support international students and graduates in the UK. At TheGradStory, we know that an international student's path is filled with excitement and challenges. Our platform was created to help them navigate this journey with confidence and clarity.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who can use TheGradStory?",
    answer:
      "TheGradStory is tailored for international students and graduates from all nationalities in the UK. We aim to guide international students and graduates through their academic and professional journey in the UK, ensuring they have the resources and support they need to succeed.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I sign up for TheGradStory?",
    answer:
      "You can easily sign up by clicking the 'Log In' button on our homepage, selecting the 'New to TheGradStory? Sign up' option and following the registration process.",
  },
  {
    question: "What makes TheGradStory different from other job searching platforms?",
    answer:
      "Our platform is built on real experiences. Founded by former UK international students, we offer personalised, practical support grounded in the realities of studying and working in the UK.",
  },
  {
    question: "Is there a subscription fee?",
    answer:
      "Yes, TheGradStory operates on a subscription basis. For just £9.99/month, you can enjoy unlimited access to all TheGradStory features, from crafting the perfect CV to finding your dream sponsored job.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I try the platform before subscribing?",
    answer:
      "Yes, we have a limited-time 7-day free trial that allows new users to explore TheGradStory subscription at no cost for seven days. Sign up today and start crafting your future!",
  },
];

export const topicFAQs = {
  queries: [],
  LIVING_IN_THE_UK: [
    {
      question: "How do I learn more about British culture before moving to the UK?",
      answer:
        "To understand the culture better, you should follow BBC News, British influencers and creators on social media, and watch movies and TV series from the country.",
    },
    {
      question: "What are some cultural differences I should be aware of?",
      answer:
        "British culture values politeness, punctuality, and queuing. It's essential to familiarise yourself with local customs, social etiquette, and standard practices to adapt smoothly to life in the UK.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the healthcare system like, and do I need health insurance?",
      answer:
        "The UK has a National Health Service (NHS) that provides free healthcare to residents. International students on a Student Visa visa pay an Immigration Health Surcharge (IHS) as part of their visa application, which grants access to NHS services.",
    },
    {
      question: "What should I do in case of an emergency?",
      answer:
        "In case of a medical emergency, call 999 for ambulance services. For non-emergency medical issues, you can visit a local GP (General Practitioner) or use the NHS 111 service for advice. Make sure you know the emergency contacts for your university as well.",
    },
    {
      question: "How should I look for accommodation in the UK?",
      answer:
        "Accommodation options include university halls of residence, private rented housing, and homestays. The best way to look for accommodation in the UK is to find an area near your university and choose a suitable budget. Selecting university accommodation in the beginning can make your transition to a new country easier.",
    },
    {
      question: "How can I set up a mobile phone plan in the UK?",
      answer:
        "You can choose between pay-as-you-go (PAYG) plans and monthly contracts. Major mobile network providers include EE, Vodafone, O2, and Three. To set up a contract, bring your passport and proof of address.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the public transportation system like in the UK?",
      answer:
        "The UK has an extensive public transportation system, including buses, trains, and subways (Tube in London). Students can benefit from discounted travel cards like the 16-25 Railcard or regional student bus passes.",
    },
  ],
  STUDYING_IN_THE_UK: [
    {
      question: "How do I know I chose the best university?",
      answer:
        "Choosing the best university depends on various factors that align with your personal and academic goals. Consider academic reputation, course content, facilities, location, graduate employability, student support services, feedback from alumni and current students, and accreditation and industry links.",
    },
    {
      question: "What are the entry requirements for studying in the UK?",
      answer:
        "Entry requirements vary by course and institution but generally include academic qualifications and English language proficiency.",
    },
    {
      question: "How do I find the right person to ask about a university I want to attend?",
      answer:
        "You can participate in your university of choice 'Open Days' events and ask the lecturers and university staff questions. You can also find people who have attended the university through word-of-mouth, LinkedIn, or Facebook groups.",
    },
    {
      question: "What documents do I need to apply for a UK student visa?",
      answer:
        "To apply for a UK student visa, you typically need a valid passport, a Confirmation of Acceptance for Studies (CAS) from your university, proof of financial support, proof of English language proficiency, and a Tuberculosis (TB) test result (if applicable).",
    },
    {
      question: "What support services are available for international students?",
      answer:
        "UK universities offer various support services, including academic advising, career counselling, mental health services, and international student offices.",
    },
    {
      question: "How can I get involved in campus life and make friends?",
      answer:
        "Universities offer various clubs, societies, and events for students to join. Participating in these activities is a great way to meet new people, make friends, and immerse yourself in the campus community.",
    },
    {
      question: "Will my university help me with my career prospects?",
      answer:
        "Most UK universities offer various services to help with career prospects, including career counselling, job placement assistance, CV and cover letter workshops, interview preparation, internship and job fairs, networking events, and access to job boards and employer connections.",
    },
    {
      question: "Do UK universities have placements?",
      answer:
        "Many UK universities offer placements or work experience in their degree programs. These placements can be integrated into the course or offered as optional opportunities. They provide practical experience in a relevant field and can enhance your employability.",
    },
    {
      question: "What are the job prospects for international students in the UK?",
      answer:
        "International students have job opportunities in the UK, especially in IT, engineering, healthcare, finance, and more. Universities often have career services to help students find internships and jobs.",
    },
  ],
  NETWORKING: [
    {
      question: "What is the best way to network and build professional connections in the UK?",
      answer:
        "Networking can be done through university events, professional organization’s events, alumni networks, and online platforms like LinkedIn. Joining clubs, attending seminars, and participating in internships also help build connections.",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Is it easy to make new friends or network in the UK? Can I find like-minded people easily with similar interests?",
      answer:
        "Networking in the UK could be relatively easy and a lot of fun. Universities provide numerous opportunities to get to know your peers and classmates better. Independent companies also organize networking events and meet-ups. Always participate in events from reputable sources in safe locations.",
    },
  ],
  WORKING_IN_THE_UK: [
    {
      question: "Can I work while studying in the UK?",
      answer:
        "Yes, international students on a student visa can work up to 20 hours per week during term time and full-time during vacations. However, it's important to balance work and study commitments.",
    },
    {
      question: "How can I gain work experience while studying in the UK?",
      answer:
        "Students can gain work experience through internships, part-time jobs, volunteering, and placements. Many courses also offer sandwich years or work placements as part of the curriculum.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I stay in the UK after finishing my studies?",
      answer:
        "Yes, you can stay in the UK after your studies with the Graduate Route visa. The Graduate Route visa allows international students to remain in the UK for two years (three years for PhD graduates) to look for work or start a career after completing their degree.",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is eligible for the Graduate Route visa?",
      answer:
        "International students who have completed an eligible course at a UK higher education institution and have a track record of compliance can apply for the Graduate Route visa. The course must be at the undergraduate level or higher.",
    },
    {
      question: "Do I need a job offer to apply for the Graduate Route visa?",
      answer:
        "No, you do not need a job offer. The visa is designed to give you time to find work after completing your studies.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I switch to another visa category from the Graduate Route visa?",
      answer:
        "Yes, you can switch to other visa categories, such as the skilled worker visa, if you meet the requirements for the new visa.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I extend the Graduate Route visa?",
      answer:
        "No, it cannot be extended. However, you can switch to other visa categories if you meet the requirements.",
    },
    {
      question: "How do I apply for the Graduate Route visa?",
      answer:
        "You must apply online, pay the visa application fee and the Immigration Health Surcharge, and prove that you have completed your course.",
    },
    {
      question: "After completing my studies, can I switch from a student visa to a work visa?",
      answer:
        "Yes, you can switch from a student visa to a skilled worker work visa if you have a job offer from a licensed sponsor and meet the eligibility criteria. There is also the Graduate Route, which allows you to stay and work, or look for work, in the UK for up to two years after completing your degree.",
    },
    {
      question: "How can I improve my chances of securing a job in the UK after graduation?",
      answer:
        "Improving chances involves gaining relevant work experience, building a strong CV, developing interview skills, and networking. Utilizing university career services and staying updated with industry trends is also crucial.",
    },
    {
      question: "What key cultural differences should I know when working in the UK?",
      answer:
        "Understanding workplace etiquette, communication styles, and professional norms in the UK is essential. Being punctual, respectful, and adapting to the collaborative work culture can help integrate better.",
    },
  ],
};
